AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records on Microfilm 5478 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Sub-Series 20: Federated Shop Craft Strike, 1922-1944
  - Series 20: Federated Shop Crafts Strike, 1922-1944 (Reel no.2) (Reel 22)
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 9 (Reel 22)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: July 5, 1922 - July 6, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 10 (Reel 22)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: July 2, 1922 - July 4, 1922
  - Series 20: Federated Shop Crafts Strike, 1922-1944 (Reel no.3) (Reel 23)
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 1 (Reel 23)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: June 27, 1922 - June 28, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 2 (Reel 23)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: June 24, 1922 - June 26, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 3 (Reel 23)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: June 20, 1922 - June 23, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 4 (Reel 23)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: June 14, 1922 - June 19, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 5 (Reel 23)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: June 9, 1922 - June 13, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 6 (Reel 23)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: June 6, 1922 - June 8, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 7 (Reel 23)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: June 1, 1922 - June 5, 1922
    - Shop Crafts Railroad Strike, 1922; 8 (Reel 23)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: April 22, 1922 - May 31, 1922
  - Series 20: Federated Shop Crafts Strike, 1922-1944 (Reel no.4) (Reel 24)
    - Legal Correspondence: Oklahoma, 1927; 1 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: January 5, 1927 - August 20, 1927
    - Legal Correspondence: Oklahoma, 1923-1926; 2 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: March 23, 1923 - April 30, 1926
    - Oklahoma Pardon Cases, 1926-1933; 3 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: December 6, 1926 - March 2, 1933
    - Oklahoma Pardon Cases, 1926; 4 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: January 3, 1926 - November 20,1926
    - Oklahoma Pardon Cases, 1924-1926; 5 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: November 6, 1924 - December 30, 1926
    - Oklahoma Pardon Cases, 1924; 6 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: April 1, 1924 - November 29, 1924
    - Oklahoma Pardon Cases, 1923-1924; 7 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: December 14, 1923 - March 29, 1924
    - Oklahoma Pardon Cases: Legal Briefs, 8 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: Xenophon Jones Case, n.d.
    - Legal Correspondence: Pennsylvania, 1944; 9 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: June 20, 1944 - July 28, 1944
    - Legal Correspondence: Pennsylvania, 1923-1924; 10 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: September 6, 1923 - July 26, 1924
    - Legal Correspondence: Pennsylvania, 1923; 11 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: March 21, 1923 - September 4, 1923
    - Legal Correspondence: Tennessee, 1924-1929; 12 (Reel 24)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: April 24, 1924 - June 6, 1929
  - Series 20: Federated Shop Crafts Strike, 1922-1944 (Reel no.5) (Reel 25)
    - Legal Correspondence: Tennessee, 1922-1929; 1 (Reel 25)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: September 13, 1922 - February 29, 1924
    - Legal Papers: Tennessee, 2 (Reel 25)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C
    - Legal Correspondence: Texas, 1924-1928; 3 (Reel 25)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: June 11, 1924 - November 8, 1928
    - Legal Correspondence: Texas, 1922-1924; 4 (Reel 25)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: September 29, 1922 - May 23, 1924
    - Pardon Cases: Miscellaneous, 1924; 5 (Reel 25)
    - R.E.D. vs Certain Carriers, 1922; 6 (Reel 25)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: Transcript of Legal Proceedings. June 20, 1922
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey et. al. vs. various classes of employees, 1922; 7 (Reel 25)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: Transcript of Legal Proceedings. July 6, 1922, Vol. I
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey et. al. vs. various classes of employees, 1922; 8 (Reel 25)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: Transcript of Legal Proceedings. July 7, 1922, Vol.II
    - Official Strike Bulletins and Circulars, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 10 (Reel 25)
      Code no. MC-0-3-131-C: Undated
- Sub-Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922
  Reels 26-40. Correspondence, minutes, exhibits and petitions regarding the second 1921 wage negotiations involving the railway shop craft unions and every major U.S. railroad. Conducted in the context of the 1921 recession and with the involvement of a Ra
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.1) (Reel 26)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 26)
      Code no. MC-132-3B-1: Peoria and Pekin Union Railroad. November 18, 1921 - February 27, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 26)
      Code no. MC-178-3B-2: Toledo, Peoria and Western Railroad. November 18, 1921 - February 6, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 26)
      Code no. MC-113-3B-3: Nashville, Chattanooga and St. Louis Railroad. November 23, 1921 - February 18, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 26)
      Code no. MC-65-3B-4: Green Bay and Western Railroad. November 18, 1921 - August 9, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 26)
      Code no. MC-82-3B-5: Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad. November 19, 1921 - May 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 26)
      Code no. MC-160-3B-6: St. Louis-San Francisco Railroad. November 18, 1921 - February 10, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 26)
      Code no. MC-436-3B-7: Akron, Canton and Youngstown Railroad. November 19, 1921 January 18, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 26)
      Code no. MC-30-3B-8: Chicago and Alton System Federation. November 18, 1921 - June 17, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 26)
      Code no. MC-108-3B-9: Missouri Pacific Railroad. November 18, 1921 - March 30, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1922; 10 (Reel 26)
      Code no. MC-27-3B-10: Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad. February 23, 1922 - May 16, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.2) (Reel 27)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 27)
      Code no. MC-27-3B-10: Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad. November 23, 1921 - February 8, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 27)
      Code no. MC-54-3B-11: Grand Trunk Railroad. November 16, 1921 - June 20, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 27)
      Code no. MC-121-3B-12: Norfolk and Western Railroad. November 22, 1921 - June 7, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 27)
      Code no. MC-10-3B-13: Boston and Maine Railroad. November 19, 1921 - March 13, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 27)
      Code no. MC-24-3B-14: Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville Railroad. November 15, 1921 - March 10, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 27)
      Code no. MC-130-3B-15: Pere Marquette Railroad. November 18, 1921 - June 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1922; 7 (Reel 27)
      Code no. MC-130-3B-15-1: Pere Marquette Railroad. February 6, 1922 - May 6, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.3) (Reel 28)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 28)
      Code no. MC-98--3B-16: Minneapolis, St. Paul and Saulte Ste Marie. November 19, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 28)
      Code no. MC-452-3B-17: St. Paul Bridge and Terminal Railroad. November 19, 1921 - May 9, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 28)
      Code no. MC-414-3B-18: St. Paul Union Depot Railroad. November 19, 1921 - March 25, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 28)
      Code no. MC-416-3B-19: Minnesota and International Railroad. November 19, 1921 - March 14, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 28)
      Code no. MC-97-3B-20: Minneapolis and St. Louis Railroad. November 19, 1921 - February 27, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 28)
      Code no. MC-34-3B-21: Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis and Omaha Railroad. November 19, 1921 - March 9, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 28)
      Code no. MC-67-3B-22: Great Northern Railroad - November 19, 1921 - March 16, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 28)
      Code no. MC-451-3B-23: Duluth Union Depot and Transfer Railroad. November 19, 1921 - January 30, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 28)
      Code no. MC-392-3B-24: Lake Superior Terminal and Transfer Railway. November 19, 1921 - January 31, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.4) (Reel 29)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 29)
      Code no. MC-122-3B-25: Northern Pacific Railroad. November 19, 1921 - March 15, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 29)
      Code no. MC-415-3B-26: Minnesota Transfer Railroad. November 19, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 29)
      Code no. MC-48-3B-27: Erie Railroad. November 19, 1921 - June 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 29)
      Code no. MC-7-3B-28: Atlanta Joint Terminal Railroad. November 19, 1921 - February 28, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 29)
      Code no. MC-38-3B-29: Denver and Rio Grande Railroad. November 19, 1921 - June 24, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 29)
      Code no. MC-467-3B-30: King Street Terminal Railroad. November 19, 1921 - February 16, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 29)
      Code no. MC-386-3B-31: Toledo Terminal Railroad. November 19, 1921 - December 27, 1921
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 29)
      Code no. MC-182-3B-32: Union Pacific Railroad. November 17, 1921 - February 23, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.5) (Reel 30)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 30)
      Code no. MC-182-3B-32: Union Pacific Railroad. November 17, 1921 - January 20, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 30)
      Code no. MC-22-3B-33: Chicago, Great Western Railroad. November 22, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 30)
      Code no. MC-1-3B-34: Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railroad. November 19, 1921 - April 7, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 30)
      Code no. MC-76-3B-35: Indiana Harbor and Belt Railroad. November 19, 1921 - March 30, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 30)
      Code no. MC-86-3B-36: Lehigh Valley Railroad. November 5, 1921 - March 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 30)
      Code no. MC-6-3B-37: Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad. November 14, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 30)
      Code no. MC-33-3B-38: Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad. November 19, 1921 - April 1, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 30)
      Code no. MC-14-3B-39: Belt Railway Co. of Chicago. November 16, 1921 - February 24, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 30)
      Code no. MC-214-3B-40: Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad. November 15, 1921 - June 20, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.6) (Reel 31)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 31)
      Code no. MC-45-3B-41: Duluth and Iron Range Railway. November 19, 1921 - February 17, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 31)
      Code no. MC-187-3B-42: Western Maryland Railroad. November 18, 1921 - June 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 31)
      Code no. MC-115-3B-43: New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad. November 15, 1921 - May 26, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 31)
      Code no. MC-115-3B-44: Boston Terminal Railroad. November 15, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 31)
      Code no. MC-29-3B-45: Chesapeake and Ohio Railway. November 19, 1921 - June 14, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 31)
      Code no. MC-5-3B-46: Ann Arbor Railroad. November 15, 1921 - February 28, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 31)
      Code no. MC-47-3B-47: Elgin, Joliet and Eastern Railway. November 19, 1921 - February 24, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 31)
      Code no. MC-224-3B-48: Chicago, Memphis and Gulf Railroad. November 29, 1921 - December 15, 1921
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 31)
      Code no. MC-74-3B-49: Illinois Central Railroad. November 21, 1921 - February 18, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 10 (Reel 31)
      Code no. MC-39-3B-50: Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad. November 14, 1921 - March 18, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.7) (Reel 32)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 32)
      Code no. MC-61-3B-51: Gulf, Mobile and Northern Railroad. November 19, 1921 - May 17, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 32)
      Code no. MC-350-3B-52: Duluth, South Shore and Atlantic Railway. November 19, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 32)
      Code no. MC-347-3B-54: Copper River and Northwestern Railway. November 22, 1921 - March 22, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 32)
      Code no. MC-223-3B-55: Duluth, Winnipeg and Pacific Railroad. November 19, 1921 - March 10, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 32)
      Code no. MC-100-3B-56: Missouri, Kansas and Texas Railroad. November 18, 1921 - March 3, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 32)
      Code no. MC-15-3B-57: Buffalo and Susquehanna Railroad. November 19, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 32)
      Code no. MC-171-3B-58: Trinity and Brazos Valley Railroad. November 19, 1921 - March 9, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 32)
      Code no. MC-152-3B-59: Rutland Railroad .November 15, 1921 February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 32)
      Code no. MC-77-3B-60: International and Great Northern Railroad. November 19, 1921 - March 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 10 (Reel 32)
      Code no. MC-37-3B-61: Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad. November 16, 1921 - March 28, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.8) (Reel 33)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 33)
      Code no. MC-21-3B-62: Central Vermont Railway. November 20, 1921 - June 20, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 33)
      Code no. MC-23-3B-63: Central of Georgia Railway. November 21, 1921 - March 12, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 33)
      Code no. MC-206-3B-64: Chicago, Peoria and St. Louis Railroad. November 16, 1921 - March 27, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 33)
      Code no. MC-53-3B-65: Ft. Worth and Denver City Railway. November 19, 1921 - June 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 33)
      Code no. MC-20-3B-66: Colorado and Southern Railroad. October 18, 1921 - February 28, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 33)
      Code no. MC-157-3B-67: Southern Pacific Railroad. November 19, 1921 - February 28, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 33)
      Code no. MC-120-3B-68: New York, Ontario and Western Railroad. November 17, 1921 - April 6, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 33)
      Code no. MC-190-3B-69: Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad. November 18, 1921 - March 8, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.9) (Reel 34)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 34)
      Code no. MC-2-3B-70: Atlantic Coast Line Railroad. November 22, 1921 - March 8, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 34)
      Code no. MC-111-3B-71: Lehigh and Hudson River Railway. November 23, 1921 - February 9, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 34)
      Code no. MC-26-3B-72: Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul Railway. November 19, 1921 - May 19, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 34)
      Code no. MC-118-3B-73: New York, Chicago and St. Louis Railway. November 16, 1921 - March 8, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 34)
      Code no. MC-69-3B-74: Hocking Valley Railroad. November 10, 1921 - March 29, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 34)
      Code no. MC-116-3B-a75: New York Central Railroad. November 15, 1921 - May 11, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 34)
      Code no. MC-87-3B-76: Lake Erie and Western Railroad. November 23, 1921 - March 29, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 34)
      Code no. MC-11-3B-77: Boston and Albany Railroad. November 28, 1921 - March 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 9 (Reel 34)
      Code no. MC-181-3B-78: Toledo and Ohio Central Railroad. November 22, 1921 - March 29, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 10 (Reel 34)
      Code no. MC-136-3B-79: Pittsburg, Lake Erie Railroad. November 15, 1921 - March 9, 1922
  - Series 21: Wage Negotiations, 1921-1922 (Reel no.10) (Reel 35)
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 1 (Reel 35)
      Code no. MC-81-3B-80: Kansas City Southern Railroad. November 18, 1921 - April 7, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 2 (Reel 35)
      Code no. MC-19-3B-81: Central Railroad of New Jersey. November 14, 1921 - March 30, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 3 (Reel 35)
      Code no. MC-8-3B-82: Buffalo, Rochester and Pittsburg Railroad. November 15, 1921 - March 12, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 4 (Reel 35)
      Code no. MC-125-3B-83: Norfolk Southern Railroad. November 21, 1921 - February 23, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 5 (Reel 35)
      Code no. MC-9-3B-84: Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. November 15, 1921 - March 29, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 6 (Reel 35)
      Code no. MC-31-3B-85: Cincinnati, Indianapolis and Western Railroad. November 7, 1921 - April 25, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 7 (Reel 35)
      Code no. MC-129-3B-86: Pennsylvania Railroad. November 26, 1921 - May 2, 1922
    - 2nd 1921 Wage Increases and Decrease Negotiations: Correspondence, Conference Minutes, 1921-1922; 8 (Reel 35)